跟蹤衛星
監視獲取
我們被監視著
We are being watched.
政府有一套秘密設備…
The government has a secret system,
一台每時每刻監視你的機器
a machine that spies on you every hour of every day.
主要威脅
我設計這個機器偵測恐怖行動
I designed the machine to detect acts of terror,
無關人群
主要威脅
但它卻看到了一切
but it sees everything,
無關人群
普通人捲入的暴力犯罪
violent crimes involving ordinary people.
政府認為這些人無關緊要
The government considers these people irrelevant.
我們不敢茍同
We don't.
無關人群
為逃避官方追捕，我們秘密行動
Hunted by the authorities, we work in secret.
主要威脅
無關人群
你不可能找到我們
You will never find us,
主要威脅
無關人群
但無論是受害者還是罪犯
but victim or perpetrator,
攝像監控
一旦你的號碼出現，我們就會找到你
if your number's up, we'll find you.
疑犯追踪
第四季        第三集
-=TLF字幕组=-
翻译：猫在江湖 飞翔的鸡 JasonLee lydia萌
校对：lydia萌   统筹：饭离烨
特效：飞翔的鸡  果子酱
紐約警局
NYPD.
我的天，怎麼回事？
Oh, my God. What happened?
你在幹什麼？
What the hell are you doing?
抓壞蛋
Catching the bad guys.
三輛警車馬上就到
Yeah. We had three RPM's coming.
你懂什麼叫支援嗎？
You know, a little thing called backup?
有時我們要等支援，不開槍
You know, sometimes we wait for it instead of shooting people,
以免在曼哈頓市中心造成恐慌
'causing mayhem in the middle of Manhattan.
今天可真是熱
It's hot as hell out here.
我得給大家節約點時間
Figure I'd save us all some time.
聽著，你現在不是獨行俠了
Listen, you're not a lone wolf anymore, pal.
你是警察，得敬畏你的工作
You're a cop, and you need to start respecting the job.
帶警徽是要遵守規章制度的
There are rules and regulations that come with that badge.
說的好像你沒違反過一樣
Like you haven't bent those rules before?
可我不再犯了
Yeah, well, I don't anymore.
你知道還有誰遵守制度嗎？新隊長
You know who else doesn't? The new captain.
真是稀奇
Well, that was novel.
眾目睽睽之下擊傷罪犯？
Shooting a perp in front of hundreds of witnesses?
真有你的
Subtle.
這傢伙可能餘生
The guy's probably gonna need crutches
都要拄枴杖了
for the rest of his life.
這是你這個月第三還是第四次
What is that, the third or fourth guy
打傷人膝蓋了，萊利？
you kneecapped this month, Riley?
第四次，長官
Fourth, ma'am.
槍法那麼準
I suppose I should give you points
我都想表揚你了
for being such a good shot.
你們是去調查鮑曼謀殺案的
You were supposed to be working the Bowman homicide.
這算怎麼回事？
What the hell were you doing
在市中心追鬧事癮君子？
chasing a druggie smash and grabber in midtown?
我們在追一條線索
We were working a developmental.
找死的線索嗎？
Into what, an early grave?
全市都有我們的線人
We got CI's all over town.
那些線人幫你們結過案嗎？
Those CI's help you close any cases yet?
警務數據系統的數據很難看
The CompStat numbers are an embarrassment.
上兩個月兇殺案上升了20％
Homicides are up 20% in the last two months.
我都想辭職了
I'm ready to fire me.
怎麼回事，先生們？
What's going on, gentlemen?
天氣很熱，隊長，火氣也大
It's a heat wave, Captain. Tempers flare.
城市狀況開始變差了
The city's taking a turn for the worse.
我們得更加努力
We need to do a better job
事先解決這些狀況
of getting out in front of this thing.
我要確認一下，你們是跟我合作還是跟我作對？
I need to know, are you guys working with me or against me?
我們只想履行職責，隊長
We just want to do our job, Captain.
那就趕緊出去
So get your asses out there
幹點正事給我看看
and show me what you can really do.
是的，長官
Yes, ma'am.
你，穿名貴西裝這位
Hey, you in the fancy suit.
你現在是隊裏的一員
You're part of a team now.
不能再像緝毒警那樣亂來了
No more narco cowboy nonsense,
還有，這幾天別給我亂開槍
and try not to shoot anyone for a few days.
聽到了嗎？
You hear me?
清清楚楚
Loud and clear.
既然聽到了，那就幹活吧
You heard what she said. We got work to do.
別緊張，萊諾
Relax, Lionel.
聽著，神奇先生
Listen, Mr. Fabulous.
我得付房屋貸款，贍養費
I got a mortgage, alimony,
過幾年孩子也要上大學了
and a kid going to college in a few years.
看到這地方了？
You see this place?
這是我的飯碗
This is my livelihood.
而且充滿了官僚主義
And it's filled with too much bureaucracy
缺少實際行動
and not enough direct action.
這就是我的生活，警探
This is my real life, Detective.
不是什麼超級英雄的掩護身份
Not some superhero cover identity.
好吧
Okay.
我明白了
I hear you.
才怪
Yeah.
不，我說真的
No, I'll work on it.
我花了二十年
I've spent the past two decades
一直在學如何不守規矩
learning how not to color inside the lines.
可能需要點時間去調整
May take me a second or two to figure it out.
我是萊利
Riley.
萊利警探，我們有新號碼了
Detective Riley, we have a new number.
不是時候，教授
Now's not the best time, Professor.
我在工作
I'm at work.
避開起疑心的上司
Circumventing suspicious employers
也是我們的新挑戰之一，約翰
is part of our new challenge, John.
請盡快
Please hurry.
<i>上，大熊</i>
Go get it, Bear.
上，快上
Go get it. Go get it.
<i>抓住它，大熊</i>
Go get 'em, Bear.
<i>抓住它</i>
Go get 'em.
肖小姐，別這樣
Ms. Shaw, please.
它不需要這種鼓勵
He doesn't need any more encouragement.
你不希望它找到？
Don't you want him to catch it?
在新辦公室找死老鼠內臟？當然不希望
Not if it involves finding rat entrails in our new office, no.
大熊，<i>過來</i>
Bear, hier.
機器幫我們找到了新辦公室
While the machine may have given us a place of operation,
但它解決不了我們的經濟狀況
it didn't account for our financial situation.
恐怕你的飯錢和房租要開始
I'm afraid your meals and rent are going to have to start
從你的實際薪水裏扣了
coming out of your actual paychecks.
好在我現在打兩份工
Well, it's a good thing I'm working two jobs.
化妝品櫃檯工資少得可憐
The makeup counter pays like crap.
你知道一雙高檔高跟鞋有多貴嗎？
And do you know how expensive a nice pair of heels are?
簡直是搶錢
What a racket.
等我獲取到其他資金再說吧
Until I access some auxiliary funds,
現在我們別無選擇
we have no choice
只能將就現在身份的社會經濟狀況
but commit to our identities' socioeconomic status.
好吧
Copy that.
這個月就吃拉麵和兩塊錢的牛排吧
Ramen and two buck chuck for the rest of the month.
我們得快點
We'll need to make this fast.
我現在在新隊長和搭檔的黑名單上
I'm on the new captain's hit list and my partner's.
怎麼，你又開槍打人了？
What, did you shoot somebody else?
<i>你得更小心點，約翰</i>
You have to be more careful, John.
機器給我們設計的身份
The identities that the machine created for us
非常珍貴，應心存感激
are precious commodities not to be taken for granted.
外面真熱
It was hot out.
不提了
Never mind.
說說新號碼吧
Let's hear about that new number.
安德烈·庫珀
Andre Cooper.
在布朗克斯區出生長大
Born and raised in The Bronx.
做過碼頭工，現在是專業社交顧問
Former longshoreman turned professional social liaison.
社交什麼？
A social what?
專業約會顧問
A professional wingman.
男人自己勾搭不到女人的時候
He's the guy people hire
就可以請他這種人
when they can't pick up women on their own.
為什麼要放棄工會工作
Why leave a union gig
<i>去教絕望男人搭訕技巧</i>
to teach desperate men pick-up tricks?
我建議去近距離看看庫珀怎麼幹的
I suggest we get close to Cooper's operation and find out.
你是說偽裝成客戶？
You mean go undercover as a client?
不行，芬奇
Not it, Finch.
別擔心，裏斯
Oh, don't worry, Reese.
哈羅德和我覺得
Harold and I decided
我們得找一個
that we needed somebody
人際交往能力更強
with a few more people skills
髮膠更少一點的人
and a little less hair gel.
- 我有手機
- 別用那個
- I have a phone. - Not that one.
用這個
Use this.
那傢伙在哪？
Where the hell is this guy?
別緊張，法斯克
Relax, Fusco.
他很可能是個只會誇誇其談的騙子
He's probably just some con artist who's in over his head.
好好玩吧
Have some fun with it.
又不是你假裝需要專業協助
You're not the one pretending to need professional help
才能約會
to get a date.
那你上次約會是什麼時候，萊諾？
And when was the last time you had a date, Lionel?
♪那男人，那男人，那男人♪
♪ what a man, what a man, what a man ♪
♪就是那個男人♪
♪ what a mighty good man ♪
♪對，就是他♪
♪ yes, he is ♪
♪那男人，那男人，那男人♪
♪ what a man, what a man, what a man ♪
專業協助來了
Looks like professional help just arrived.
♪我要好好關心一下♪
♪ I wanna take a minute or two and give much respect to ♪
♪這個改變我的男人♪
♪ to the man that's made a difference in my world ♪
♪多數男人只是玩玩♪
♪ and although most men are hos ♪
♪但他卻與眾不同♪
♪ he flows on the down low ♪
♪我從未聽說他有過別的女孩♪
♪ 'cause I never heard about him with another girl ♪
你好，我是法斯克
How you doing? Fusco.
你朋友哈羅德沒提醒我
Your friend Harold didn't warn me
你是什麼情況
what I was dealing with here.
應該事先說清楚的
Could have been a little more up-front.
什麼？
Excuse me?
他給你買了兩天的套餐
He bought you a two-day package.
但你這情況至少也得五天啊
This is more like a-- like a five-day situation.
也許得七天
Maybe seven.
你干保險的？
You're in insurance?
對，沒錯
Yeah, that's right.
是網上業務？
Is it like an online business?
我不想跟你扯淡
Hey, look, I don't need to take this crap.
來，來，坐
Come on, come on, come on, sit down.
♪那男人，那男人，那男人♪
♪ what a man, what a man, what a man ♪
♪就是那個男人♪
♪ what a mighty good man ♪
見一個女人
think about meeting women
就像是推銷自己
like you're selling yourself.
懂嗎？
All right?
得讓她們感覺你很努力
They need to feel like you've made an effort,
而不是早上一起床
that you didn't just roll out of bed
隨便在襯衫外面套上昨天的西裝
and throw on yesterday's suit with a new shirt.
牛啊，還真是昨天的西裝
Holy crap. That is yesterday's suit.
我是來教你
I am here to teach you
如何獲取女人的欣賞
how to earn a woman's affections,
而不是玩弄她們
not trick her into it,
而你，朋友，你得更努力
and you, my friend, you need to do better.
- 是嘛？
- 是的
- Oh, yeah? - Yeah.
你覺得這身衣服能討人喜歡？
'Cause if this is you dressing to impress,
我可不喜歡
well, I am not,
女士們更不會喜歡
and the ladies aren't gonna be either.
說到點上了
He's got a point.
我這身哪不對？
What's wrong with what I'm wearing?
我都不知道從何說起了
I don't even know where to start.
褪色，用料簡陋
The faded color. The fireproof fabric.
糟糕的領帶
That sad tie.
如果要在這裏評選「最不時尚先生」
If you're going for the least modern man in this room,
恭喜你，你贏了
congratulations, you have won.
我還贏過幾場拳擊比賽呢
I've also won a few boxing matches, too.
你想來幾輪嗎？
You want to go a few rounds?
來吧
Come on.
該幹活了
Let's get to work.
去哪？
Where are we going?
購物
Shopping.
希望你信用卡額度夠高
I hope you have a decent line of credit.
♪那男人，那男人，那男人♪
♪ what a man, what a man, what a man ♪
♪就是那個男人♪
♪ what a mighty good man ♪
我想我知道是誰要殺他了
I think I know who's gonna kill our guy.
誰？
Who?
我
Me.
你有什麼事，葛洛弗小姐？
What may I do for you, Ms. Groves?
這裏真是…
It's very...
我想你要說的詞是「簡樸」
I think the word you're looking for is spartan.
沒錯，而且非常隱蔽
Yes, and well-hidden.
它給了你和孩子們一個美好的新家
She gave you and the kids a nice, new home.
我再問你一遍
I'll ask again.
機器需要你幫個忙
The machine needs a favor.
不
No.
它知道你會懷疑它的動機
She knew you'd doubt her motives.
讓它補償你吧
Let her make it up to you.
它保證這對你們三個人都有益處
She promises it will be worth something to all three of you.
機器想要什麼？
What is it that the machine wants?
我還不知道
I don't know yet.
它沒給我多少線索
She gave me very little to go on.
在撒瑪利亞的監視下
She can't talk to me the way she used to
它不能像以前那樣和我交談
with Samaritan watching,
但我知道從哪下手
but I do know where to start.
好極了，又是一次徒勞
Excellent. A wild goose chase.
我更願意當作一次尋寶遊戲
I'd like to think of it more as a scavenger hunt.
你的搭檔呢？
Where's your partner?
呃，在重新訪問一個案件的嫌疑人
Um, re-interviewing suspects on a case.
戒煙貼好用嗎？
How is that working out for you?
你看呢？
Pfft. How's it look?
一塊根本不夠
One patch is not enough.
沒錯，從你被咬壞的指甲
Yeah, I could have told you that
就能看出來
from your chewed-up fingernails.
談話技巧不錯嘛，警探
That's a pretty good parlor trick, Detective.
執行外勤任務的時候用過嗎？
You putting those skills to work out in the field yet?
溫迪·蒙哥馬利謀殺案，我有一條線索
I got a lead on Wendy Montgomery's murder,
那個房產經紀人在下班回家路上被槍殺
that realtor who was shot walking home from work.
<i>看起來像行兇搶劫</i>
Looked like a mugging.
是的，她丈夫是首要嫌疑人
Yeah, her husband was the prime suspect,
但我們沒有任何真正的線索
but we didn't have any real leads.
現在有了
Well, we do now.
他一直在跟一個著名殺手通郵件
He's been emailing with a known hit man.
你怎麼弄到這些郵件的
How did you get these?
還記得我一直在跟的那些線索嗎？
You know those developmentals I've been working on?
你非要知道更多嗎？
You really need to know more than that?
如果你要玩遊戲，可以
If you want to play fast and loose, fine,
不過得保證證據確鑿地抓住他
but make sure you nail him with something solid.
明白，長官
Copy that, ma'am.
<i>芬奇？</i>
Finch?
<i>芬奇？你藏哪兒去了？</i>
Finch, where are you hiding?
你發現安德烈·庫珀的新線索了嗎？
Did you discover anything new about Andre Cooper?
<i>我搜了一遍他的郵箱</i>
Well, I scrubbed through his inbox,
發現庫珀和一個客戶的前妻之間的郵件
and I found some emails between Cooper and a client's ex-wife.
他們在上床
They were sleeping together.
不是明智的商業決策
Not the best business decision.
那位客戶也是這麼想的
The client didn't think so either, so he sent
安德烈·庫珀
個人約會顧問
所以他發了一堆郵件，威脅要殺掉<i>約會顧問</i>
a bunch of emails threatening to kill our wingman.
我會在Yelp上給你一條差評，混蛋
這麼說是庫珀先生的情感糾葛
So Mr. Cooper's romantic entanglements
讓他置身危險之中了
have put him in danger.
我打開他的語音信箱之前也是這麼想的
That's what I thought until I got into his voicemails.
<i>他十天前被法庭傳喚了</i>
Our boy was subpoenaed ten days ago.
為什麼？
What for?
調查紐約集裝箱碼頭的
An investigation into a missing gun shipment
槍支貨物失蹤案件
from the New York Container Terminal,
正是在庫珀以前工作的地方
Cooper's old workplace.
就在集裝箱失蹤的那段時間
That container disappeared around the same time
庫珀辭掉了薪水豐厚的碼頭工作
our boy swapped his well-paying dockworker gig
開始幹這個不穩定的職業
for his sketchy career helping socially incompetent men
幫有社交障礙的男性搭訕女性
pick up women.
聽起來是個可靠的調查方向
Sounds like a solid avenue of investigation.
對，我實在需要個幫手，芬奇
Yeah, I could really use an extra hand here, Finch.
所以我們派出了法斯克警探
Well, that's why we recruited Detective Fusco.
呃，法斯克比我們預計的
Yeah, uh, Fusco's gonna be a bit more preoccupied
要更忙一點
than we thought.
我不知道
I don't know.
這都不是我了
This just ain't me.
現在還有人戴袖扣嗎？
And who wears cufflinks anyway?
自己怎麼扣上這玩意？
How do you put these things on by yourself?
沒錯，袖扣和剪裁得體的長褲
You're right, cufflinks and perfectly tailored pants
正適合想結識女人的笨人
are for suckers that just want to meet women.
不然給你弄套運動服搬個按摩椅試試
Maybe we could get you a tracksuit and a Barcalounger.
運動服有什麼不對？
What's wrong with a tracksuit?
你是運動明星嗎，萊諾？
Are you a track star, Lionel?
我可不覺得，用點心吧
I didn't think so. Try harder.
這一套真的管用嗎？
Does this stuff really work?
相信我
Trust me.
你以為我一起床就是這樣嗎？
You think I just roll out of bed looking like this?
我不知道
I don't know.
女人們可不會排隊等著
Women aren't lining up to date a guy
跟把足球衫當休閒裝穿的男人約會
who alternates football jerseys for his casual wardrobe.
不至於吧，夥計
Easy, pal.
難道你不喜歡女孩子
Look, don't you love it
頭髮梳得漂漂亮亮的來約會嗎？
when a girl fixes her hair up all nice for a date, hmm?
為你穿著性感的裙子？
Wears that hot dress just for you?
你以為10厘米的高跟鞋舒服嗎？
You think four-inch heels are comfortable?
從沒想過
Never really gave it any thought.
穿起來疼得要命，但女人就是要穿
They probably hurt like hell, but women wear them anyway.
為什麼？因為男人喜歡
Why? Because guys like it.
所以，我們也要給女士們一點尊重
So let's give the ladies a little respect
讓她們知道你也在努力
and show them that you can make an effort too.
一旦吸引到她們的注意，如何留住人就取決於你了
Once you have their attention, it's up to you to keep it.
那個你也要教我吧？
You gonna show me how to do that too?
一樣一樣來吧，花花公子
One thing at a time, Don Juan.
不如就從扔掉那雙富樂紳鞋子開始
Why don't we start with you losing those Florsheims.
穿著像警察似的
You look like a cop.
你上次交女朋友是什麼時候的事了，萊諾？
When's the last time you had a girlfriend, Lionel?
不關你事
None of your business.
知道嗎？
See?
如果你不敞開心扉，我就沒法幫你
I can't help you if you don't open up.
我就像是那方面的心理醫生
I'm like a therapist in that way.
謝了，醫生，我不感興趣
No thanks, doc. I'm not interested.
好吧，她叫朗達
All right, her name was Rhonda.
好的
All right.
我們約了好幾次
We went out a bunch of times,
但她就…就慢慢淡下來了
but she just-- just kind of faded away.
反正我這種事從來都沒戲
These things never work out anyway.
看，這就是你的問題
See? That's your problem right there.
- 你憤世嫉俗
- 我沒有憤世嫉俗
- You're cynical. - I'm not cynical.
我只是覺得人很可怕
I just know that people are terrible.
哦，天哪
Oh, man.
一個憤世嫉俗的厭世者
A cynical misanthrope.
我…我不知道保險工作
Look, I-I don't know what they did to you
會讓你幹什麼
at that insurance job,
可你顯得很刻薄
but it made you sour,
女人不喜歡刻薄
and women do not like sour.
我不知道怎麼跟你解釋
Well, I don't know how to break it to you,
但我不是那種純真可愛的類型
but I'm not a unicorn and rainbows kind of guy.
我不是說要你天真無邪
Look, I'm not saying that you need to be naive.
只要少一點悲觀就好
Just a little less pessimistic.
沒見你手上戴戒指
I don't see a ring on your finger.
你有什麼故事嗎？
What's your story?
我現在的精神狀態不適合談戀愛
I'm not in a mental state to be in a relationship right now.
自己做不來的，就去教別人，對吧？
Those who can't do, teach, right?
那你怎麼幹上這行的？
So how'd you get in the business?
我擅長跟人打交道
I'm good with people.
這一點還有待驗證
Yeah. That still remains to be seen.
我總幫朋友們結識女孩子
Uh, I was always helping my friends meet girls,
有次一個哥們讓我幫他搭訕
and one time my buddy asked me to help him on the side,
說會付錢給我
said he'll pay.
生意就此誕生
A business is born.
兩年之後，他結婚了
Two years later, he's getting married.
所以，抱點希望吧
So have some hope.
我希望…
I got hope...
你趕緊結束演講
that this speech is gonna end soon.
一直活在過去
You keep living in the past,
只會孤獨終老
you're gonna wind up alone.
但也無法逃脫過去
Can't run away from your past either.
埃格雷先生，很榮幸見到您
Mr. Egret, it's an honor.
我讀過很多您的故事，先生
I've read a lot about you, sir.
您的海灣之旅，您與黑水公司的合作
Your tour in the Gulf, your work with Blackwater.
這位辣妹是誰？
Who's the hottie?
不關你的事
She's none of your concern.
一把AT4，反坦克肩發彈藥系統
An AT4, anti-tank shoulder launched munitions system
84毫米彈頭，300米射程
with 84-millimeter rounds and a firing range of 300 meters.
真是把好武器
Nice piece of machinery.
談好的5萬
50,000, as agreed.
很高興跟傳奇人物做生意
It was nice doing business with a legend.
<i>希望日後能再次合作</i>
Hope we get to work together again someday.
埃格雷先生，您介意告訴我們
Mr. Egret, would you mind telling us
打算用這導彈做什麼嗎？
what you plan to do with the missile?
就是好奇而已
Just out of curiosity.
我非常介意
You know? I would mind very much.
我們要用它做什麼？
What are we gonna do with this?
還不知道
I don't know yet,
但我真的很喜歡你展現出的另一面
but I am truly enjoying this new side of you, Harold.
太出人意料了
It's very unexpected.
敢問你是怎麼弄到這筆錢的？
Dare I ask how you procured that amount of money?
就通過非法入侵什麼的
It involved some breaking and entering.
也就是說這些人會繼續在黑市上
I take it these men will just continue to sell munitions
出售武器彈藥？
on the black market?
有點信心，哈羅德
Have a little faith, Harry.
<i>放下箱子</i>
Put the case down.
<i>不許動！</i>
Don't you move!
<i>看見沒有？</i>
You see?
它依然在工作，哈羅德
She's still doing her job, Harold.
一直在守望
Always watching.
該走了
Time to go.
♪ 你實在是 ♪
♪ you're just ♪
♪ 太美妙了 ♪
♪ too marvelous ♪
♪ 美妙得無法用語言形容 ♪
♪ too marvelous for words ♪
♪ 容光煥發 ♪
♪ like glorious ♪
♪ 魅力無窮 ♪
♪ glamorous ♪
♪ 還有那老式的做派，風情萬種 ♪
♪ and that old standby, amorous ♪
♪ 一切都是這麼美好 ♪
♪ it's all too wonderful ♪
<i>好了，我們上</i>
Okay, here we go.
除非有人搭話，否則不要開口
Don't speak unless spoken to.
我來負責互相介紹
I'll handle the intros.
- 好的，不過…
- 不要說話
- Okay, but-- - No talking.
要傾聽，要有眼神接觸
Listening. Make eye contact.
要有禮貌，不過別當受氣包
Be polite, but don't be a doormat.
要微笑，但不要過度
Smile, but not too much.
你肯定不想看起來像神經病
You don't want to look like a crazy person,
但最重要的是…
but most of all...
要享受其中，萊諾
have fun, Lionel.
♪ 永遠寫入詞典中 ♪
♪ to ever be in Webster's dictionary ♪
♪ 我借來一用 ♪
♪ and so I'm borrowing ♪
♪ 是鳥兒們吟唱的情歌 ♪
♪ a love song from the birds ♪
♪ 唱出你是多麼美妙 ♪
♪ to tell you that you're marvelous ♪
♪ 美妙得無法用語言形容 ♪
♪ too marvelous for words ♪
真抱歉
I'm sorry.
這一回合真不順利
Well, that went poorly,
不過我聽說在某些文化裏
although I have heard in some cultures
把酒水灑到女人身上是一種求偶儀式
spilling drinks on a woman is a mating ritual.
我剛準備不恨你了
I was just starting not to hate you.
你得放鬆，兄弟
You got to relax, man.
你把這事當成工作一樣
You're treating this like some kind of a job.
可能我就是有點遲鈍吧
Guess I'm a little rusty.
你認識她？
You know her?
不認識，不過快了
No, but I will soon.
安德烈！
Dre!
嗨，米奇！哇！
Hey, Mick! Oh, wow.
- 這都快…
- 差不多一年了
- It's been... - Almost a year.
米奇是我在碼頭的老朋友
Mick is an old friend from the docks.
老相識了
We've known each other a long time.
是啊，可不
Yeah, I'd say.
好久沒來這種地方了
Way before you'd ever come in a place like this.
是啊，你怎麼來這了？
So true. So what got you here?
我表兄弟住這家酒店
Ah, my cousin's staying at the hotel.
我就下來喝一杯
I thought I'd come down and get a quick drink.
這位是誰？客戶嗎？
Who's this guy? Client?
這是萊諾
This is Lionel.
新客戶
He's new.
是一個熟人介紹的
It was gift from a friend, uh, a guy I knew.
放鬆啦，酷哥
Hey, don't worry, killer.
當初還是安德烈幫我約到我老婆的
Andre actually hooked me up with my wife.
他會是你見過最棒的把妹達人
He's the best pick-up artist you'll ever meet.
你住在市中心區對吧？
Hey, you live in midtown, right?
市區東邊？
Midtown East?
對呀，沒錯
Yeah, that's right.
約個時間一起吃飯吧
We got to grab a meal sometime soon.
見到你太棒了，夥計，回見
It's great seeing you, man. Take care.
我看見了
I saw that.
糟了
Oh, boy.
嘿，小子
Hey, pal.
勾搭我女朋友？
Checking out my girl?
我沒發現她名花有主
You know what? I didn't realize she was anyone's girl.
是嘛
Yeah, right.
怎麼…
What the--
紐約警局，今晚你就別想好好過了
NYPD. You're cut off for the rest of the night.
明白嗎？
You understand me?
你到底是什麼人？
Who the hell are you?
你做完口供了？
You finish making your statement?
是的
I did.
你有什麼要說的嗎？
Do you have a statement,
比如為什麼在工作方面對我撒謊？
like why you lied to me about what you do for a living?
你在調查我嗎，萊諾？
Am I under investigation, Lionel?
你犯了什麼事需要被調查嗎，安德烈？
Did you do something to warrant investigation, Andre?
不，當然沒有，你在迴避問題
No, of course not. You're avoiding the question.
我是法斯克
Fusco.
<i>等一下，萊諾</i>
Hold up, Lionel.
<i>我認為這個號碼可能是個罪犯</i>
I think our number might be a perp after all.
<i>你發現了什麼？</i>
What'd you find?
紅鉤區有件麥洛·雅各布斯謀殺案
Open homicide in Red Hook on a man named Milo Jacobs.
被害人九個月前在碼頭當保安
He worked security on the docks up until nine months ago,
安德烈·庫珀   個人約會顧問
紐約貨運碼頭集裝箱丟失
跟槍支失蹤是同一時期
around the same time that gun shipment went missing.
我這裏有麥洛和庫珀間的通話記錄
And I have got phone calls here between Milo and Cooper.
可能是他們一起偷走了貨物
Maybe they stole that shipment together.
是我搭檔問我情況
That's my partner checking in.
然後呢？
Well?
我說謊是因為警察不會雇約會顧問
I lied because cops don't hire wingmen.
那幫傢伙要是知道了，肯定要揍扁我的
The guys find out, they'll bust my chops to my grave.
今天還沒結束
Well, the day's not done,
你朋友又提前付錢了，那麼…
and your friend paid in advance, so...
什麼？你想繼續？
What? You want to keep going?
你是個英雄，我們該利用好這個名頭
You're a hero. We should capitalize on that.
咱們趕下一場
I have another event we could catch.
還能糟到哪去呢？
What's the worst that could happen?
裏面有主廚的口供
The chef's confession is on there.
你抓了溫迪·蒙哥馬利的丈夫
You got Wendy Montgomery's husband.
幹得好啊，萊利
- Well done, Riley. - Hmm.
眼睛上的傷我就不過問了
I won't ask about the eye.
你搭檔在哪？我也想祝賀他
Where's your partner? I want to congratulate him too.
法斯克在追另一宗案子
Fusco's taking the lead on another case.
接下來呢？
What's next?
汽車代理商中槍案
That car dealership owner who got shot?
他挪用自己公司的錢
He was embezzling money from his own company.
你認為他的僱員與此事有關？
You think his employees were in on it?
我認為他們找到了他藏錢的地方
I think they found out where he was hiding the money
然後殺了他
and killed him for it.
我查了他們的信用卡記錄
I tapped into their credit reports.
<i>自從他們老闆死後</i>
They've been spending a lot of money
他們一直在大把花錢
since their boss' death.
我是否需要知道
Do I want to know
你是怎麼搞到信用卡記錄的？
how you got those credit reports?
上午不順嗎？
Bad morning?
哦，我包裏現在還有煙味
Oh, my pocketbook still smells like cigarettes.
戒煙搞得我煩得要死
Quitting has me edgy as hell,
不過要麼用膏藥，要麼看醫師
but it was either the patch or a hypnotherapist,
我才不信什麼空話大道理
and I don't believe in that hippie nonsense.
或許我們能把你的煩躁轉化成優勢
Maybe we can use that edginess of yours to our advantage.
有點意思
I'm intrigued.
說來聽聽
Tell me more.
我告訴過你不要再調查下去了
I told you no more developmentals.
我正在調查一條線索…
I was working up a lead--
你的工作效率在下滑，萊利
Your numbers are down, Riley.
如果你結不了案
If you don't start closing more cases,
我就把你調去看管證據倉庫
I'm gonna ship you off to evidence lockup
再找個能結案的人來干
and find someone who can.
我是萊利警探
I'm Detective Riley.
你們哪個先跟我談？
Which one of you wants to go first?
鮑曼的案子我已經被審問過了
I've already been questioned about Mr. Bowman's murder.
我那時一無所知，現在也一無所知
Didn't know anything then. Don't know anything now.
有謠言說鮑曼先生脾氣不太好
I heard a rumor Mr. Bowman had a bit of a temper.
還聽說他總是遷怒於你，你厭惡透了
I also heard you were sick of him taking it out on you.
是啊，換成是你，也會煩透的
Yeah, well, you'd be sick of it too.
業績不好，他就衝我們大喊大叫
He'd scream at us if we didn't sell enough
如果我們沒努力改善也是
or if we weren't pushing upgrades.
又不是每個人都想要汽車霧燈
Yeah, well, not everyone wants fog lights.
看見我那暴脾氣的長官了沒？
My ballbuster of a captain out there?
她往死裏催我結這個案子
She is all over me about closing up this case
一定要在今天之前
before the end of the day.
<i>我只是擔心我的飯碗</i>
I'm just worried about my job,
所以咱們談個條件怎麼樣？
so what do you say we make a deal?
我不知道你什麼意思
I don't know what you mean.
- 我一無所知
<i>- 得啦，連尼</i>
- I don't know anything. - Come on, Lenny.
你倆找到了鮑曼藏錢的地方
You guys found out where Bowman was keeping the money,
然後殺了他，對嗎？
and you killed him for it, right?
- 不是這樣的
- 當然是這樣
- That's not true. - Sure, it is.
我只是不知道你倆哪位
What I don't know is which one of you
想先跟我談條件
wants to make a deal with me first.
什麼條件？
What kind of deal?
你們幫我結案，分我一半的錢
You help me close up this case, give me half the money,
然後就一筆勾銷
and we'll make this all go away.
我們還可以確定讓連尼背黑鍋
Hell, we'll even make sure that Lenny takes the fall for it.
因為反正巴裏會說都是你的主意
Because Barry's gonna say it was all your idea anyway.
他撒謊！這都是巴裏的主意！
He's a liar! This was all Barry!
分一半錢？
Half?
一半
Half.
好吧，但一定算巴裏的責任，放過我，行不？
Fine, but this all falls on Barry, not me, right?
這算結案了嗎，長官？
Does that work for you, Captain?
看來你又結了個案子，萊利
Looks like you closed another case, Riley.
繼續努力吧，餐具大獎等你拿
Keep it up, you'll get that set of steak knives.
很久沒這麼開心了
The most fun I've had in a while.
- 演得不錯
- 你也是
- Good game. - You too.
很想慶祝一下
Love to celebrate,
不過既然你正走運，這個重案就交給你了
but since you're on a roll, it's a priority homicide.
剛來自專員辦公室
It just came in from the Commissioner's Office.
非法街頭小販撤回了口供
Illegal street vendor recanted his statement.
他被威脅了
The vendor's scared.
你得比威脅他的人更厲害才行
Be scarier than the guy who made him clam up.
遵命，長官
Yes, ma'am.
看見沒，萊諾
You see, Lionel?
目光接觸
Eye contact.
<i>對哦，萊諾</i>
Yeah, Lionel.
婦女慈善活動是遇到女士們的絕佳途徑
Women's charities are a great way to meet ladies.
女士人數更多，還可以打著慈善的名頭
You're always outnumbered, and it's for a good cause.
不覺得有點狡猾嗎？
Isn't that a little tacky?
我更喜歡稱之為「戰略」
I prefer the word "Strategic."
別擺弄袖口了，靚仔
Stop primping, gorgeous.
有人在看你
Somebody's watching you.
在拍賣會旁邊的女士
Lady by the silent auction.
來點微笑
Great smile.
我們怎麼辦？
What do we do?
她已經主動給你機會了
She's already doing all the work for you.
快過去吧
Now off you go.
你是否感覺有點緊張
Are you feeling a little exposed
手持反坦克導彈
having an anti-tank missile in our possession
在曼哈頓中心，還是只有我在緊張？
in the middle of Manhattan, or is it just me?
撒瑪利亞絕不會找一個帶著AT4的大學教授的
Samaritan won't be looking for a college professor with an AT4.
我擔心的不是撒瑪利亞
It's not Samaritan I'm worried about.
那是誰？
Then who?
國土安全局，紐約警局
Homeland Security. NYPD.
女巡警
An errant meter maid.
埃格雷？
Egret?
你是？
And you are?
「該死的達賴喇嘛」，我是傑瑞
The freakin' Dalai Lama. I'm Jerry.
我是被你們聯繫過的另一個傢伙派來的
The guy who was sent by the other guy you contacted
他說你們要把貨出手？
about the thing you wanted to sell?
你有買家？
You have a buyer for us?
我原以為埃格雷長得會更兇一點
I thought Egret would be more, uh, badass.
畢竟你名聲在外啊
I mean, you got that rep, you know?
可你看起來沒那麼壯
You don't look so tough.
那是因為我只有兩種狀態，傑瑞
That's because I have only two modes, Jerry...
冷靜和憤怒
calm and furious.
很少有人能看到後者
It's a rare person that sees the latter
還能活著跟別人談起
and lives to talk about it.
好吧
Okay.
明白了
I gotcha.
大夥兒淡定嘛
Everyone relax now.
跟我來
Follow me.
<i>我也喜歡</i>
I-I like it too.
我不懂這是個什麼，但是我喜歡
I don't know what it is, but I like it.
得了，法斯克
Oh, come on, Fusco.
直接問她要電話號碼吧
Just ask her for her number already.
我們還得搞清楚你的新朋友是不是罪犯
We need to figure out if your new buddy's a killer.
<i>等一下</i>
Wait a sec.
<i>這人是誰？</i>
Who's this guy?
碼頭工
Longshoreman.
法斯克，帶上安德烈，快從後門離開
Fusco, grab Andre and go out the back exit now.
我很抱歉，我得走了
I-- I'm sorry. I-I have to go.
你在幹嘛？為什麼不問她要電話號碼？
What are you doing? Why didn't you get her number?
你有危險
You're in danger.
我們要離開這，快點
We need to get you out of here right now, come on.
嘿
Hey there.
胃抽筋真要命
Oh, wicked stomach cramps.
退後！
Back up!
米奇，你不清楚你在幹什麼
Mick, you don't know what you're doing.
恐怕恰恰相反，夥計
I'm afraid you got that the other way around, pal.
帶他上車，兩個都帶上
Get him in. Bring 'em both.
我們走
Let's go.
我們走，快！
Let's go, move!
我回到畫廊
You know, I went back to the art gallery.
那個假安保也跑了
That fake security guard, he high-tailed it out of there.
他們一定想從安德烈身上得到什麼
They must want something from Andre.
不然，他早就被殺了
Otherwise he'd already be dead.
不好意思
Sorry.
米奇和庫珀一定是一起偷了那批貨
Mickey and Cooper must have stolen that shipment together.
我敢說有人出賣了對方
I bet someone double-crossed someone.
我們得跟蹤米奇的貨車
We need to track Mickey's van.
<i>你現在是警察</i>
You're a cop now.
<i>可以全權進入區域警覺系統了？</i>
Full access pass to domain awareness?
多虧了「老大哥」，我們也能監視別人了
Thanks to Big Brother, we can be watching too.
追 蹤 車 牌      紐  約    M70346
根據時間段標記，在20分鐘之前
This has been time-stamped 20 minutes ago.
追 蹤 車 牌      紐  約    M70346
我們走
Let's move.
我不能去，肖
I can't, Shaw.
莫雷諾隊長交給我一樁重案
Captain Moreno handed me a priority homicide.
萬一沒及時找到法斯克
What do you think this is gonna be
你覺得會有什麼後果？
if we don't get to Fusco soon?
她盯我盯得很緊
She's got me under a microscope.
如果她發現了我的真實身份
If she figures out who I really am,
撒瑪利亞也會，那我們都完了
Samaritan will too, and we'll all be dead.
我是萊利
Riley.
遵命，長官
Yes, ma'am.
我正在去調查小販的路上
I'm on my way to interview the vendor now.
呃，這人有點難找，長官…
Well, he's been a little bit hard to find, ma'am--
好吧，不過我要帶上狗
Fine, but I'm taking the dog.
你想告訴我你讓我攤上什麼事了嗎？
You want to tell me what you got me involved in?
抱歉，萊諾
I'm sorry, Lionel.
我本以為米奇不會再出現了
I thought Mickey was out of my life for good.
你們這群傢伙幹了什麼？
What did you ass clowns do?
我沒有
Not me.
是米奇
Mickey.
有個叫多米尼克的商人給他錢
Some dealer named Dominic paid him off
讓他偷走一集裝箱的槍
to disappear a container full of guns.
他只是從系統中刪除了集裝箱
He just deleted it out of the system.
地方檢察官懷疑米奇
DA suspects Mickey's involved.
他們想讓我作證，我不肯
They want me to testify. I said I wouldn't.
為什麼？
How come?
你知道為了正義而背棄朋友
You know how hard it is to turn your back on your friends
有多難嗎？
because it's the right thing to do?
知道
Yeah.
我也算經歷過
I know a little bit about that.
那你就能明白我為什麼沒招
Then you understand why I didn't say anything.
說什麼悄悄話吶？
What are you girls gossiping about?
安德烈正跟我說你有多蠢
Andre here was just telling me what a moron you are
居然綁架警察
for kidnapping a cop.
<i>確實有點意外</i>
Yeah, that came as a bit of a surprise.
什麼時候跟條子混一起了，安德烈？
Since when are you hanging out with cops, Dre?
萊諾是我的客戶，他是好人
Lionel's a client, and he's a good man.
<i>放了他</i>
Let him go.
太晚了，兄弟
It's too late for that, buddy.
快說，我干零活這事
Now just tell me what you've been saying to the DA
你跟地檢官說了什麼？
about my little side job?
都說了我什麼也沒說
I already told you. Nothing.
我也希望如此
I want to believe that.
我們認識15年了
You've known me for 15 years.
你就像我兄弟，你知道我說的是實話
You're like a brother. You know I'm telling the truth.
你曾經是我兄弟，但你拋棄了我
You were my brother, but you abandoned me.
因為你愈發貪婪
Because you got greedy.
你身居正位，卻幹了不法勾當
You took an honest job and you turned it dirty.
我只是談生意
I made a business deal.
是啊，跟幫派罪犯談生意
Yeah, with a criminal street gang.
現在還要讓好人幹壞事
Now you got good men doing bad things.
好人總會幹壞事
Good men do bad things all the time.
不，你比那些奸商還差勁
No, you're worse than those dealers,
因為你對朋友下手，比如麥洛
'cause you turned on your friends, like Milo.
我也是迫不得已
I did what I had to do.
如果你殺了警察
Look, if you kill a cop,
政府就會通緝你
the feds are gonna come looking for you.
不會
No.
他們會通緝你
They're gonna come looking for you,
因為我會佈置成這樣
'cause that is how I'm gonna set it up.
動手吧
Get 'em ready.
我什麼都沒看見，我告訴他們…
I saw nothing. I told them--
被害人死亡當晚你就在紅鉤區
You were in Red Hook the night the victim died.
我們追蹤了你的手機
We traced your cell.
我沒在那
I wasn't even there.
我沒說謊
I'm not lying.
那我幫你好好想想？
What if I help your memory?
是這樣的
Here's how this works.
要是你想起有用的事
You remember something useful,
我就給你這個信封
and I give you this envelope
買你一個手袋
in exchange for one of these lovely handbags.
手袋是正品，對吧？
These are genuine, right?
把這錢包賣我
Sell me this purse,
你就能展開新生活
and you get to start a new life.
但首先你得告訴我你看見了什麼
But first you need to tell me what you saw.
你確定我們能信任這些先生？
You're certain we can trust these gentlemen?
信任他們？當然不能
Trust 'em? Of course not.
不能信任任何人，埃格雷
You can't trust anyone, Egret.
你的世界不是這樣麼？
What world do you live in?
這下有意思了
This is gonna be interesting.
要是我們死了可就沒意思了
It's going to be a lot less interesting once we're dead,
葛洛弗女士
Ms. Groves.
大熊，我數到三
Okay, Bear, on three.
一，二…
One, two...
<i>調查，</i> 大熊
Zoek, Bear.
<i>調查</i>
Zoek.
我雇了朋友，確保這集裝箱
I hired a friend to make sure
絕不會到達目的地
this container never reaches its destination.
別擔心
Don't worry.
你們很可能淹水之前就中暑死了
You'll probably die of heat stroke before you drown.
我們走
Let's go.
鼎鼎大名的埃格雷先生
The famous Mr. Egret.
你彷彿是憑空出現
It seems you materialized out of nowhere.
然後就無所不在了
Now you are everywhere.
怎麼做到的？
How is that?
我非常注重隱私
I'm a very private person.
好吧
Yes.
我也一樣
I am as well.
你們很幸運能找到我朋友，傑瑞
You're lucky you know my friend, Jerry.
我們不信任外人
We don't trust outsiders.
15萬
150,000.
你要數嗎？
Would you like to count it?
我和埃格雷先生都相信錢夠數
Mr. Egret and I are certain the money's all there.
不，我不能這麼做
No, I can't do this.
- 哈羅德…
- 對不起
- Harold-- - I'm sorry.
這導彈不賣了
This missile is no longer for sale.
我還以為你是說話算話的人，埃格雷先生
I thought you were a man of your word, Mr. Egret.
賣導彈給犯罪團伙就另當別論
Not if it involves selling a rocket launcher to the mob.
任何罪犯都不行
Any mob.
這是我的底線
That happens to be a line I'm not willing to cross.
它太瞭解你了，哈羅德
She knows you so well, Harold.
現在我們就能一石二鳥了
Now we get to kill two birds with one stone.
要不要把他們綁起來以防萬一？
Should we tie 'em up just in case?
做這些事意義何在，葛洛弗女士？
What was the point of all this, Ms. Groves?
做這麼荒唐的事能幫助什麼人？
How did this ridiculous journey help anyone?
讓我給你看
Let me show you.
你說的對
You're right.
袖扣還是有點好處的
These cufflinks are good for something.
這招真炫
Neat trick.
你到底是什麼人，萊諾？
Who are you really, Lionel?
相關第三方
A concerned third party.
現在怎麼辦？
What now?
我覺得你朋友說的中暑不是開玩笑的
I think your friend wasn't kidding about the heat stroke.
我們不可能從這衝出去
There's no way we can bust out of here.
<i>喂！</i>
Hey!
喂！
<i>喂！</i>
Hey!
會有人聽見嗎？
You think anyone can hear us?
你在這幹嘛？
What are you doing here?
我？你在這幹嘛？
Me? What are you doing?
你不是扮警探去了嗎？
I thought you were out playing detective.
我的重案線索指向我們的號碼
My priority homicide traced back to our number.
那個賣假包的人
The guy selling knock-off handbags
看見一個碼頭工殺了被害人
saw a dock worker kill their victim.
你接手的是麥洛·雅各布斯的案子？
That homicide you picked up was Milo Jacobs?
就是他
That's our guy.
法斯克呢？
Where's Fusco?
在這附近
Here somewhere.
大熊，<i>調查</i>
Bear, zoek.
米奇和他手下還躲在某處
Mickey and his goons are still out there.
你去找法斯克和約會顧問
You get Fusco and the pick-up artist.
我去搜他們
I'm gonna go hunting.
<i>喂！</i>
Hey!
法斯克？
Fusco?
<i>我們在這！</i>
We're in here!
你來了真好，搭檔
Nice of you to show up, partner.
我就要結束今天的第三個案子了
I was about to close my third case of the day.
得確保你不會沒等我
Wanted to make sure you didn't die
有機會吹牛就先死了
before I had a chance to brag about it.
米奇還沒落網，我要抓住他
Mickey's still out there. I'm gonna get him.
從來都不給夠子彈
They never give you enough ammo.
小心，萊諾！
Look out, Lionel!
<i>大熊, 安靜</i>
Bear, heel!
多謝支援
Thanks for the backup.
隨時效勞
Anytime.
身手不錯，約會顧問
Nice moves, wingman.
你也是
You too.
幫個忙好嗎？
Hey, guys, give me a hand here, will you?
快走
Come on.
這個漂亮的山寨包是你買的，萊利？
I have you to thank for this lovely knockoff, Riley?
顏色不適合我
It wasn't my color.
聽說你之前的包裏都是煙味
I heard your old one smelled like an ashtray.
尼古丁貼片
每天一次，每次一片
這些又是什麼人？
Who are these mooks?
拉脫維亞團伙
Latvian mob.
我們接到匿名電話
We got an anonymous phone call.
在唐人街的廠房裏發現了他們
Found 'em in a Chinatown sweatshop.
很奇怪的案子
Very strange case.
他們都被打傷了膝蓋
They were all shot in the knees.
要不是事先知道
If I didn't know any better,
我還以為是你幹的呢，萊利
I'd think it was your doing, Riley.
今天大家幹得不錯
Great work today, guys.
你真是力轉乾坤
You really managed to turn things around.
多謝誇獎，隊長
Thank you, Captain.
今晚我請客喝酒
Drinks on me tonight.
我，呃…
I, uh...
看來你終於學會當好警察了
I guess you figured out how to be a good cop after all.
需要過程，萊諾
It's a process, Lionel.
今晚喝酒的事，我…
Listen, about those drinks tonight, I, uh--
我已經有約了
I got somewhere to be.
庫珀衝破你的約會前線了？
Cooper came through on the dating front?
這邊
Right over there.
謝謝你
Thank you.
我馬上回來，好嗎？
I'll be back. Okay?
好
Okay.
一杯蘇打水，一杯夏敦埃，謝謝
A club soda and a glass of chardonnay, please.
你把酒灑她身上了嗎？
You spill your drink on her yet?
在某些文化裏這是求偶儀式
That's a mating ritual in some cultures.
我要指證米奇和他同夥
I'm testifying against Mickeynd his boys.
你說的對
You were right.
無法逃脫過去
You can't run from your past,
起碼不挨槍子是逃不過的
at least not without getting shot at, right?
記住，要有眼神接觸，自信點
Remember, eye contact, confidence.
要享受其中
Make sure you're having fun.
安德烈，我能搞定
Andre, I got this.
我知道你行
I know you do.
不過如果你還需要複習課程
But if you ever need a refresher course,
記得打給我
you give me a call.
沒問題
Done.
給你
Here you go.
謝謝你
Thank you.
歡迎回來
Welcome back.
拉脫維亞團伙不再需要這些物資了
Our Latvian friends won't be needing these supplies anymore.
這是機器計劃的？
This was the machine's plan?
它堅信要救你的無關號碼，哈羅德
She believes in saving your irrelevant numbers, Harold.
而在你無法獲取
And while you can't access
以前的銀行賬戶期間…
any of your old bank accounts right now...
情況也在好轉
things are looking up.
機器能提供我們
The only way the machine
這種資金支援的唯一方法
could give us this kind of financial assistance
就是以撒瑪利亞不會發現的方式
was to do so in a way that Samaritan would never discover.
不義之財，善加利用
Ill-gotten gains put to good use.
也許你該給再它一次機會了
Maybe it's time you give her a second chance.
那枚導彈怎麼辦？
What will we do with the missile?
我相信我們會有辦法的
I'm sure we'll think of something.
疑犯追踪
谢谢观赏
TLF字幕组欢迎你
TLF中文字幕站 http://sub.eastgame.org/
微博地址：http://weibo.com/tlfsubs
豆瓣小站：http://site.douban.com/127446/